<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Under the Hood on</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/</link><description>Recent content in Under the Hood on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Release Notes</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/release-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/release-notes/</guid><description>Build 1020221118 #
Fixed an issue with stats displaying incorrect color over 1k value. Fixedd an issue where add journal entry box is disabled after successful addition. Added snackbar message to successful journal entry completion. Build 1020221117 #
Users can now long press on an expense item for additional actions (reverse, duplicate, and share). Users can now short press on an expense item for additional information (including notes), which implements this feature request.</description></item><item><title>Technical Details</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/technical-details/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/technical-details/</guid><description>Development Environment #
IntelliJ IDEA Android Studio #
Native Android development necessitates IntelliJ IDEA Android Studio.
Programming Language #
Kotlin #
Kotlin&amp;hellip;
Is officially preferred by Google as the language for Android over Java.
Compiles directly to Java bytecode on Java Virtual Machine to maintain compatibility with legacy platforms.
Has Kotlin Multiplaform feature, which enables client-side (JavaScript) and iOS compilation.
vs. Java #
Kotlin provides many benefits over Java. Below are three most important ones to this developer.</description></item><item><title>Future Plans</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/future-plans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/future-plans/</guid><description>Development Improvements #
CI/CD #
Not having to manually deploy to Google Play Store for every new release would be nice.
Code Style Enforcement #
At the moment linting is optional. One day I plan to clean up my code and enforce lint rules. One day.
Error Handling #
At the moment I am certain there are uncaught exceptions. I intend to catch them all.
Replace Static Fields with String Resources #
I plan to replace static string fields with @StringRes for better testability.</description></item><item><title>Internal Testing</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/internal-testing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/under_the_hood/internal-testing/</guid><description>Thank you for participating in the exclusive internal test program of Reconcile the Android app. This page will explain to you the app’s purpose, its current implementation, and your role in the test process.
Important Disclosures #
This app is in its early stages of development and should not be relied upon for any tasks. Your data may be wiped at any time without notice. Additionally the app has not undergone any stringent security audits.</description></item></channel></rss>