<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Use Cases</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/use-cases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/use-cases/</guid><description>Roommates #
You are on the lease and responsible for payments related to rent, utilities, shared meals, and so forth. Your roommate pays you in installments throughout the month. You need a way to track the balance.
Partners #
You and your partner maintain separate finances and want to keep track of shared expenses (housing, utilities, transport, food, and so forth) and has an effectively perpetual open tab.
Friends #
You are planning an epic trip (or maybe just a shared meal) with your friends and need a way to track costs and repayments.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/features/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/features/</guid><description>Secure and Easy Google Sign-In #
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to sign up manually and keep a different set of passwords for Reconcile.
Offline Support #
You can continue to view the ledger and add new journal entries even when you are offline.
Realtime Updates #
When you are online, any changes you make will be instantly reflected in the cloud. Even if you lose your phone, you will never lose your Reconcile ledger.</description></item><item><title>How to Use</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/how-to-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/how-to-use/</guid><description>Download the App #
Use this link to download the app from Google Play Store.
Note that you may need to request to be added to the internal test list before you can access the app.
Log In #
If you are on an Android phone signed into your Google account, logging in is as easy as tapping the &amp;ldquo;Sign In&amp;rdquo; button. Your ledger stays with the associated Google account. This means that when you sign in on another device using the same Google account, you will see the latest version of your ledger regardless of your location.</description></item><item><title>Rules of Accounting</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/rules-of-accounting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/overview/rules-of-accounting/</guid><description>Entry Immutability #
Once a journal entry is entered onto the ledger, it cannot be changed.
If you discovered a mistake on an existing journal entry, enter another journal entry with the opposite value to cancel it out. You can even add notes to the journal entry to remind yourself (and the other party) the reason.
No Backdating #
A journal entry&amp;rsquo;s date is timestamped by the server and cannot be modified.</description></item></channel></rss>