<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Use</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/how-to-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/how-to-use/</guid><description>Log a Journal Entry #
When a shared expense takes place, fire up the app, which will display your ledger, which is currently empty. Tap the plus button to add a new journal entry. Make sure you have the correct counterparty, who is the person with whom you share the expense. The amount should be equal to the counterparty&amp;rsquo;s responsibility. If this amount is what the counterparty owes you, then tap &amp;ldquo;Debit.</description></item><item><title>Rules of Accounting</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/rules-of-accounting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/rules-of-accounting/</guid><description>Entry Immutability #
Once a journal entry is entered onto the ledger, it cannot be changed.
If you discovered a mistake on an existing journal entry, enter another journal entry with the opposite value to cancel it out. You can even add notes to the journal entry to remind yourself (and the other party) the reason.
No Backdating #
A journal entry&amp;rsquo;s date is timestamped by the server and cannot be modified.</description></item><item><title>Use Cases</title><link>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/use-cases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reconcile.endiantribe.com/docs/use-cases/</guid><description>Roommates #
You are on the lease and responsible for payments related to rent, utilities, shared meals, and so forth. Your roommate pays you in installments throughout the month. You need a way to track the balance.
Partners #
You and your partner maintain separate finances and want to keep track of shared expenses (housing, utilities, transport, food, and so forth) and has an effectively perpetual open tab.
Friends #
You are planning an epic trip (or maybe just a shared meal) with your friends and need a way to track costs and repayments.</description></item></channel></rss>